import { PrismaClient } from '@prisma/client';
const prisma = new PrismaClient();
async function main() {
  const user = await prisma.user.upsert({
    where: { email: 'ahj@gmail.com' },
    update: {},
    create: {
      name: 'Amirhossein',
      email: 'ahj@gmail.com',
      password: '123qwe',
    },
  });
  const topics = await prisma.topic.createManyAndReturn({
    data: [
      { title: 'Deutsch B1', ownerId: user.id },
      { title: 'Deutsch A2', ownerId: user.id },
      { title: 'Deutsch A1', ownerId: user.id },
      { title: 'Animals', ownerId: user.id },
      { title: 'Cities', ownerId: user.id },
    ],
    skipDuplicates: true,
  });
  console.log(topics);
  const cards = await prisma.flashcard.createManyAndReturn({
    data: [
      {front: 'der Aberglaube',back: 'superstition',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Hufeisen',back: 'horseshoe',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'beschützen',back: 'protect',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der stein',back: 'stone',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'tatsächlich',back: 'real',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Stimme',back: 'voice',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'rennen (ist gerant)',back: 'run',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Einbrecher',back: 'housebreaker',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Heim - e',back: 'home',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'klappen',back: 'work (sth work)',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'klopfen (hat geklopft)',back: 'knock',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'schießen ( schießt · schoss · hat geschossen )',back: 'shoot, kick',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Notiz - en',back: 'note',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der schaden , ¨',back: 'damage',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Vorhang, äe',back: 'curtain',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'stoßen (stößt · stieß · ist gestoßen )',back: 'run into',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'gegen',back: 'against',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'beißen (beißt · biss · hat gebissen)',back: 'bite',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'erschrecken (erschrickt · erschrak · ist erschrocken)',back: ' be scared',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der bericht, -e',back: 'report',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'beschreiben (beschreibt · beschrieb · hat beschrieben)',back: 'describe',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'berichten (berichtet · berichtete · hat berichtet)',back: 'reporting',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Serie -n',back: 'the series',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Folge -n',back: 'episode',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die staffel -n',back: 'the season',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Blut',back: 'the blood',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Operation, -en',back: 'the operation',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Figur, -en',back: 'the figures',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der König. -e',back: 'the king',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Star, -s',back: 'the star',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Abenteuer',back: 'adventure',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'verändern (hat verändert)',back: 'change',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die show, -s',back: 'the show',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Zuschauer / Zuschauerin',back: 'viewer',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Stil, -e',back: 'the style',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'veröffentlichen (hat veröffentlicht)',back: 'publish',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Sänger/ Sängerin',back: 'the singer',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Halle, -n',back: 'the halls',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'Außerhalb',back: 'Outside',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'miteinander',back: 'each other',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Song , -s',back: 'the song',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Band, -s',back: 'the band',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Hit , -s',back: 'the hit',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Sheibe, -n',back: 'the disk',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Reportage, -n',back: 'the report',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Jungend',back: 'youth',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'irgendwann',back: 'sometime',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'teilen',back: 'split',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Link, s',back: 'the link',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Humor',back: 'the humor',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'verlassen (verlässt · verließ · hat verlassen)',back: 'leave',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'reisen (ist gereist)',back: 'travel',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'außen',back: 'Outside',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'innen',back: 'Inside',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Rundfunk',back: 'the radio',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Schulter, -n',back: 'shoulders',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'heben',back: 'lift',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'achten (auf)',back: 'pay attention',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Untersuchung -en',back: 'the investigations',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'ausreichend',back: 'sufficient',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Hälfte, -n',back: 'half',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Drittel, -',back: 'a third',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Störung, -en',back: 'the disorder',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Grund, e',back: 'the reason',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'eventuell',back: 'possibly',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Einnahme (Sg.)',back: 'the taking ',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Schmerzmittel, -',back: 'the painkiller',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Krankenkasse, -n',back: 'the health insurance company',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Rat (Sg.)',back: 'the council ',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Kraft -äe',back: 'the force',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'reduzieren (hat reduziert)',back: 'reduce',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Mittel, -',back: 'the middle',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'tief',back: 'deep',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'umgehen (mit), ist umgegangen',back: 'deal (with)',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Grundlage, -n',back: 'the basics',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'meist-',back: 'most of time-',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Muskel, -n',back: 'the muscle',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'persönlich',back: 'personal',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Tempo',back: 'the tempo',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'atmen',back: 'breathe',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Wirkung, -en',back: 'the effect',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Fett, -e',back: 'the fat',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'ideal',back: 'ideal',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'ebenfalls',back: 'also',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Sache, -n ',back: 'the thing',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Ergebnis, -se',back: 'the result',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'ängstlich',back: 'fearful',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'kühl',back: 'cool',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'auf|wachen (ist aufgewacht)',back: 'wake up ',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'gleichzeitig',back: 'at the same time',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'automatisch',back: 'automatically',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'beruhigen (sich),hat beruhigt',back: 'calm down',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'mit|teilen, ( hat mitgeteilt )',back: 'to share',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Konferenz, -en',back: 'the conference',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'überprüfen',back: 'check',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'kontrollieren',back: 'check',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Schreibblock, öe',back: 'the writing pad',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Labor, -s',back: 'the laboratory',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Spritze, n',back: 'the syringe',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'die Lieferung, -en',back: 'the delivery',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Workshop, -s',back: 'the workshop',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'der Kursleiter, - / die Kursleiterin - nen',back: 'the course leader',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'schimpfen',back: 'rant',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'garantieren',back: 'to guarantee',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'lächeln',back: 'smile',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
      {front: 'das Geheimnis, -se',back: 'the secret',topicId: topics[0].id,ownerId: user.id},
    ],
    skipDuplicates: true,
  });

  console.log(cards);
}
main()
  .then(async () => {
    await prisma.$disconnect();
  })
  .catch(async (e) => {
    console.error(e);
    await prisma.$disconnect();
    process.exit(1);
  });
